喘不过气了吗
Having a little trouble catching your breath there?
不  不  我没事儿
No, no, I'm good.
要是体育老师早告诉我刻苦训练是为了这个
If my P.E. teachers had told me this is what I was training for,
我就会试着再努力点
I would have tried a lot harder.
要么去做  要么放手  没有尝试一说
"Do or do not. There is no try."
你刚引用了星战的台词吗
Did you just quote star wars?
我引用的应该是《帝国反击战》的台词
I believe I quoted Empire Strikes Back.
老天爷
Oh, my God.
我居然和一个能引用尤达大师的话的美女躺在一起
I'm lying in bed with a beautiful woman who can quote Yoda.
我爱你  佩妮
I love you, Penny.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
我只是不吐不快而已
I just wanted to put that out there.
不  我很高兴
Oh, yeah, no, I-I'm-I'm glad.
那就好
Good.
-高兴就好  -嗯
- Glad is good.  - Yeah.
没手表
No, no...
呃...已经很晚了
So, it's getting pretty late.
-我们差不多该睡觉吧  -对
- We should probably go to sleep.  - Yeah.
-对  -该睡了
- Okay.  - Yeah, probably.
-晚安  亲爱的  -晚安
- Okay, good night, sweetie.  - Good night.
生活大爆炸
第三季第十九集
莱纳德  你对巨型蚂蚁这个问题持什么立场
Hey, Leonard, where do you come down on giant ants?
谢尔顿说不可能有
Sheldon says impossible.
霍华德和我都觉得不仅可能
Howard and I say not only possible,
而且作为一种交通工具  比蝙蝠战车酷多了
but as a mode of transportation, way cooler than a Batmobile.
你忽视了平方/立方定律
You are ignoring the square-cube law.
巨型蚂蚁会被 自身的骨骼重量压垮
The giant ant would be crushed under the weight of its own exoskeleton.
而且准确来说
And for the record,
真正酷的交通工具排名应该是
the appropriate ranking of cool modes of transportation is:
喷射背包  悬滑板  传送器  蝙蝠战车 然后才是巨型蚂蚁
jet pack, hoverboard, transporter, Batmobile, and then giant ant.
有没有搞错 你们就没别的事干
Seriously? You have nothing better to do
只能坐在这里聊巨型蚂蚁存在的可能性吗
than sit around and discuss the possibility of giant ants?
他怎么了
What's with him?
估计他到了每月一次的敏感期了
Perhaps he's at a sensitive point in his monthly cycle.
你是说他来大姨夫了[与Menstruating同音]
Are you saying he's man-strating?
不是字面意义上的
Not literally.
但早在十七世纪
But as far back as the 17th century,
科学家就发现男性荷尔蒙水平 有个33天的波动周期
scientists observed a 33-day fluctuation in men's hormone levels.
有意思
Interesting.
难怪我每月中旬都会两眼泪汪汪
That might explain my weepy days in the middle of the month.
你知道我在说什么
You know what I'm talking about.
算了  不说巨型蚂蚁
Okay, forget giant ants.
巨型兔子呢
How about giant rabbits?
不管大小  我都不喜欢兔子
Big or small, I don't like rabbits.
兔子总是看似很想说话
They always look like they're about to say something,
但从来不开口
but they never do.
兔子倒是有呼吸系统 支撑巨大的体型
Rabbits do have a respiratory system that would support great size.
并且  兔子是少数哺乳动物中
And on a side note, they are one of the few mammals
阴囊长在阴茎前的
whose scrotum is in front of the penis.
也许这才是他们想谈论的
Maybe that's what they want to talk about.
莱纳德  你对巨型兔子和阴囊位置 持啥态度
Leonard, where do you stand on giant rabbits and scrotal position?
我一点都不在乎
I honestly don't care.
是吗
Really?
每次我们谈到不寻常的动物生殖器
Because every time we've talked about unusual animal genitals,
你总会有些有力且富争议性的观点
you've always had some pretty strong and controversial opinions.
你想让我说什么 我就是对这个没兴趣
What do you want from me? I just don't give a rat's ass.
有没有巨型老鼠屁屁
Would that be a giant rat's ass?
准确来说  巨型老鼠是有可能存在的
For the record, giant rats are possible.
我们能不能说点别的
Can we please talk about something else?
比如稍微跟我们生活有关 而且是地球上的东西
Maybe something vaguely related to life as we know it on this planet?
这个话题怎么样
Okay, how about this for a topic:
为什么莱纳德是个大混蛋
Why is Leonard being a giant douche?
假设大混蛋有可能存在
Assuming giant douches are possible.
当然有
Of course they are.
莱纳德就是一个
Leonard's being one.
说不定他和佩妮发生了"爱爱"口角
Maybe he's having a lover's spat with Penny.
才怪  我们没吵架
No, there was no spat.
但确实发生了点状况
Oh, but something happened.
我不想谈这个
I don't want to talk about it.
我觉得你想说  我不想听 失陪
But I sense you're going to and I don't want to hear about it. Excuse me.
你干啥了  罗密欧
What'd you do, Romeo?
往身上倒枫蜜
You pour maple syrup all over your body
问她有没有性致玩3P
and ask her if she was in the mood for a short stack?
你是不是穿她的内裤跳来跳去取悦她
Did you think it would be funny to put on a pair of her panties and jump around,
结果却把她吓着了
but it wound up just creeping her out?
什么  没有
What? No.
我只是问问  老兄
I'm just asking, dude.
没准儿呢[Raj深受其害]
It happens.
你们参加今晚的保龄球赛吗
You guys still on for bowling tonight?
当然参加
Oh, yes.
我还准备了几句垃圾话呢
In fact, I've prepared some trash talk for the occasion.
你打得跟你妈一个水准
You bowl like your mama.
不过  如果她打得很好
Unless, of course, she bowls well.
那就是  你打得跟你妈大相径庭
In which case, you bowl nothing like her.
哦  唉哟
Oh. Ouch.
这就是灼烈言辞的效果
That is what is referred to as a burn on you.
你要求她滴蜡吗
Did you ask her to start waxing?
没有
No.
你滴蜡了
Did you start waxing?
没有
No.
是不是做爱时
While making love,
你不小心拍了自己屁股  然后大声哭喊"妈咪"
did you accidentally spank your own ass and cry out, "Mommy"?
我懒得理你们
I'm walking away from you now.
他没否定哎
That wasn't a no.
看来我们猜得越来越靠谱儿了
Yeah, I think we're getting close.
你是在跟她上床的时候
Did you take a Benadryl
吃了片苯海拉明(此药会造成昏昏欲睡)然后睡着了么
and fall asleep while pleasuring her?
你可能会因此丢了小命儿哎
Because you can die that way.
牡丹花下死  做鬼也风流啊
Oh, that would be a good way to go.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi.  - Oh, hey.
太好了  佩妮 友情提示  今晚7点  保龄之夜
Good, Penny. Reminder: bowling tonight at 7:00.
噢对  保龄
Oh, right, bowling.
你要是不想来也不用勉强
You don't have to come if you don't want to.
不会啊  没那回事儿
No, no, it's okay.
说实话  没我的话你们指定输得巨惨
I mean, let's face it, you guys would get creamed without me.
确实
We would indeed.
就此特殊情况来看
In this particular case,
你纯爷们儿的气质对我们十分有利
your lack of femininity works to our advantage.
跟你聊天总是这么开心  谢尔顿
It's always nice chatting with you, Sheldon.
是讽刺吗
Sarcasm?
是毫不掩饰的轻视你
Thinly veiled contempt.
-别忘了  7点  -知道啦
- Remember: 7:00.  - Got it.
-是太平洋夏令时  -咋着吧
- Pacific Daylight time! - Bite me!
请把这纯爷们儿的气场发挥在赛场上吧
Please reserve that butch spirit for the lanes.
你不是要带自己的保龄球鞋来吗
I thought you were bringing your own bowling shoes.
这双就是我自己的啊
These are my own bowling shoes.
那你还消什么毒啊
Then what's with the disinfectant?
我脚踩过啥地方我知道
I know where my feet have been.
嗨  佩妮
Hey, Penny!
还有各位路人
And you guys.
阿尔比诺·鲍勃不能来了 所以我带了个替补来
Albino Bob couldn't make it, so I brought a substitute.
相信你们中有人认识他 威尔·惠顿 (《星际迷航》中的演员)
I believe some of you know wil Wheaton.
嗨  谢尔顿  近来如何啊
Hi, Sheldon. How's it going?
哎哟哟 这不是威尔·惠顿嘛
Well, well, well. If it isn't Wil Wheaton,
我家蜘蛛侠的敌人  绿魔
the Green Goblin to my Spider-Man.
我家伽利略的对头  教皇保罗五世
the Pope Paul V to my Galileo,
我家火狐的对手  IE浏览器
the Internet Explorer to my Firefox.
我上次纸牌锦标赛赢了你 你不会还怀恨在心呢吧
You're not still carrying a grudge because I beat you at that card tournament, are you?
我可是"臭威尔惠顿" 企业网站  互联网站和机构网站的所有人
I'm the proud owner of wilwheatonstinks.com, .net, and .org.
知道这说明什么吗
What does that tell you?
这说明你无时无刻都在想着我
It tells me that I am living rent-free right here.
准备好比赛了么
You ready to bowl?
当然准备好了
Oh, I'm ready.
我不知道斯图尔特有没有告诉你 今晚你的对手是谁
I don't know if Stuart told you what you're up against tonight,
不过站在你面前的人就是
but before you stands the co-captain of the
东德克萨斯州青年基督徒圣保龄同盟会 冠军队的联盟队长
East Texas Christian Youth Holy Roller Bowling League championship team.
7到12岁参赛组
Seven- to 12-year-old division.
佩妮打得也不错
Also, Penny's pretty good.
很好  那放马来吧
Great. Then it's on.
愚蠢的威尔·惠顿  战火就没灭过
Oh, foolish Wil Wheaton, it was never off.
好的
Yes!
常见的补中
A common spare.
保龄赛会上的"特工佳丽"
The Miss Congeniality of the bowling pageant.
在你登陆推特
Before you jump on Twitter
然后吹嘘自己那可以无视的成就之前
to tout your modest accomplishment,
看看什么叫真正的高手
watch how it's really done.
吾乃此球
I am the ball.
吾念乃其念
My thoughts are its thoughts.
其洞乃吾洞
Its holes are my holes.
好的
Yes.
推特这个吧  推特鸟
Tweet that, Tweety Bird.
我只想跟你说 我是你的粉丝
Hey, I just wanted to tell you i'm a big fan.
谢了
Oh, thanks.
你肯定被《星际迷航》的问题问得想吐了
I'm sure you're probably sick of Star Trek questions,
不过乌比·戈德堡  你有没那个啊
but Whoopi Goldberg-- you ever hit that?
啤酒啊
Ah, beer.
能让这个可怜害羞的印度男孩
The magic elixir that can turn this poor, shy Indian boy
成为耀眼人物的神奇药剂
into the life of the party.
好耶
Oh, yeah.
吃辣味奶酪薯条吗
Chili cheese fry?
好啊  我爱辣味奶酪薯条
Yes. I love chili cheese fries.
真的  你爱吃啊
Really? You love them?
是啊  怎么了
Yeah, why?
没事啊  只是很高兴听到 你对表达爱意毫无障碍
No reason. I'm just glad to hear you're comfortable saying you love something.
你真的想现在谈这事儿吗
Do you really want to get into this right now?
谈啥事儿
Get into what?
你怎么会不爱吃辣味奶酪薯条呢
Why wouldn't you love the chili cheese fries?
这么多年你一直都在吃
They've been in your life a long time.
它们让你心情大好  它们应该知道你对它们的爱
They make you happy. They deserve to know.
昨晚我只是被你吓到了  我不知道说什么好
Look, you just caught me by surprise last night. I didn't know what to say.
好  到现在给你的思考时间够久了吧
Okay, well, now you've had some time to think about it.
那你想说什么
So, what do you want to say?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
你怎么会不确定
How can you not be sure?
在这谈论这事儿不太合适
Okay, this isn't the place to have this conversation.
对啊  合适的地方是在床上
No, the place to have the conversation was in bed
在我说了"我爱你"
after I said, "I love you"
你说"谢谢  晚安"之后
and you said, "Thank you. Good night."
别逼我  莱纳德
Don't push it, Leonard.
-我没逼你  -你逼我了
- I am not pushing anything.  - You are.
你没权利决定我什么时候准备好说"我爱你"
You don't get to decide when I'm ready to say "I love you!"
原来是过早的告白问题
Ah, the premature "I love you."
我猜的是过"早"的问题  算对吗
I guessed "premature." Does that count?
佩妮
Penny.
干嘛
What?
给你的
This is for you.
冰淇淋
Ice cream?
我通过研读连环画《凯西》[一部讲述女人生活的漫画]
I've been familiarizing myself with female emotional crises.
努力想要熟悉雌性生物的感情危机
by studying the comic strip Cathy.
她一沮丧就会说"日"  然后吃冰淇淋
When she's upset, she says, "Ack!" and eats ice cream.
日啊
Ack!
你要是只猫  我就给你带千层面了
If you were a cat, I would have brought you a lasagna.
是莱纳德让你来的吗
Did Leonard send you over here?
不  自从你昨晚突然离开 我们还没说过话
No, we haven't spoken since your abrupt departure last night
害得我们昨天输给斯图尔特和他那卑鄙的参赛者威尔·惠顿
caused us to forfeit to Stuart and his dastardly ringer Wil Wheaton.
为此我很抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
我毫不自豪地承认昨天我是哭着睡着的
I'm not too proud to admit that I cried myself to sleep.
再次说声抱歉
Again, I'm sorry.
让我来告诉你吧
And let me tell you, sleep did not
有莱纳德在隔壁嘶吼摇滚歌手莫莉莎的歌
come easily with Leonard in the next room
你就很难睡着了
singing along with Alanis Morrisette.
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
不  很显然某位来大姨夫的也急需冰淇淋来解闷
No. Clearly another woman in dire need of ice cream.
好吧  谢尔顿 有没有什么安慰点的消息
All right, Sheldon, what part of this is supposed to make me feel better?
关于这一点 我自行决定了来一场复赛
The part where I tell you i've engineered a rematch
今晚重新对战斯图尔特他们
with Stuart's team for tonight.
亲爱的  我不知道
Oh, honey, I don't know.
现在和莱纳德在一起感觉怪怪的
Things are a little weird with Leonard right now.
你想让我把他踢出去吗
You want me to remove him from the team?
我是队长  我说了算
I'm the captain. I can do that.
不  没关系
No, no, that's okay.
我去和他谈谈  回来再找你吧
Just let me talk to him, and I'll get back to you.
你准备什么时候找他谈
When are you going to talk to him?
不知道
I don't know.
他在洗衣房  现在去正好
He's in the laundry room now. Now would be a good time.
我不去你就一直烦我烦到死对吧
You're n gonna leave me alone until I do it, are you?
哎呀  这还用问吗
Oh, I think we both know the answer to that question.
我觉得我们应该谈谈
I think we should talk now.
什么  不  没事
Wha...? No, it's okay.
我们不用谈  也没什么可谈
We don't have to talk 'cause there's nothing to talk about.
一切都好
Everything's good.
真的吗
Really?
那你生气不是因为
So, you didn't get all snarky
我对一碗辣味薯条说了句好话
'cause I said something nice to a bowl of chili fries?
好吧  也许我反应过激了
All right, maybe I overreacted.
我们俩感情上不太同步  那又如何
So we're in two different places emotionally. So what?
或许我比你快了一点  没关系
And maybe I'm a little ahead of you. That's fine.
其实很合理  面对现实
In fact, it makes sense, 'cause let's face it,
我爱你比你爱我多了整整两年
I've been in this relationship two years longer than you.
莱纳德  你要知道我很在乎你
Look, Leonard, you have to know how much I care about you.
可我以前就是太早说"爱你"
It's just that I've said the "L" word
结果都不欢而散
too soon before, and it didn't work out very well.
是吗
Really?
不知道那是什么情形
I wouldn't know what that's like.
对不起
I'm sorry.
但你明白我的意思
You know what I'm talking about, though.
我明白
Yeah, I do.
我们和好了吗
So, we're good?
对  我就是这个意思
Yes, that's what I'm telling you.
我们很好  好得不得了
We are good. We are great.
太好了  栅栏已补  误会已清
All right! Fence mended, problem swept under the rug.
去打保龄球吧
Time to bowl!
对  我刚刚在偷听
Yes, I was eavesdropping.
因为赌注太大了
There's a lot at stake here.
注意  选手们
Attention, all bowlers:
我强制要求穿这个参加我们的复赛
I've taken the liberty of having these made for our rematch.
"卫斯理·柯洛夏斯"
"The Wesley Crushers"?
不是指卫斯理·柯洛夏斯
No, not The Wesley Crushers.
而是卫斯理碾碎者
The Wesley Crushers.
我不明白
I don't get it.
卫斯理·柯洛夏是
Wesley Crusher was
威尔·惠顿在《星际迷航》里扮演的角色
Wil Wheaton's character on Star Trek.
还是不明白
Still don't get it.
这是个极其巧妙的双关语
It's a blindingly clever play on words.
在他所饰演的角色名后面加个复数
By appropriating his character's name and adding the S,
暗示着我们将是彻底终结卫斯理的人
we imply that we we'll be the crushers of Wesley.
好吧  抱歉亲爱的
Okay, I'm sorry, honey,
但你这样写  看起来就好像有好多粉丝
but The Wesley Crushers sounds like a bunch of people
喜欢卫斯理·柯洛夏
who like Wesley Crusher.
不  再次强调  不是卫斯理·柯洛夏粉丝群
No! Again, it's not the Wesley Crushers.
而是卫斯理·柯洛夏终结者
It's the Wesley Crushers.
如果你想表示  你将彻底打败卫斯理
No, if you want it to mean you're crushing Wesley,
就该直接写  打倒卫斯理·柯洛夏
it'd be the Wesley Crushers.
听听你们说的什么胡话
Do you people even hear yourselves?
这不是什么卫斯理·柯洛夏斯
It's not The Wesley Crushers.
也不是卫斯理粉丝群
而是卫斯理终结者
It's The Wesley Crushers.
看哪
Hey, look.
他们那队是以我名字命名的
They named their team after me.
不  这才不是...
No, it's not the...
算了
Never mind.
好了  都清楚打赌内容和赌注了
So, we're all clear on the bet and the stakes?
当然  输的一方将接受公开羞辱
Oh, yes. The losers will be publicly humiliated
具体方式由胜者选定
in a fashion to be chosen by the victor.
告诉你  我准备让你们发表篇科学论文
FYI: I plan on having you publish a scientific paper
详细说明维利科夫斯基那荒谬的假设
expounding the discredited Velikovsky hypothesis.
再次唉哟
Ouch again.
你好  谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon,
我只想告诉你
I just wanted you to know
我热切期盼着打得你一败涂地
that I'm really looking forward to wiping the floor with you.
真的吗
Oh, yes?
回应你之前  我先问你个问题
Well, before I respond, let me a you a question.
你妈妈保龄球打得好不好
Is your mother a good or poor bowler?
你先
After you.
不  你先
No, after you...
因为我们准备终结你  卫斯理
as we are  currently crushing you, Wesley.
右边球道的选手先投  这是种习惯
It's customary for the player on the right-hand lane to bowl first.
好吧
All right.
只是种习惯  并非规则
It's a custom, not a rule.
我真鄙视你
I so loathe you.
就是这样  谢尔顿
That's right, Sheldon.
要学会接受社会阴暗面
Embrace the dark side.
你根本没权利跟我这么说
That's not even from your franchise!
我想让你知道 即使我们是对立一方
I, um, I want you to know that even though we're on opposite sides,
我始终对你并无恶意
I, I bear you no ill will.
谢谢  斯图尔特  很高兴知道这点
Thank you, Stuart. It's nice to know.
对立双方的人 往往都关系非常好
People from opposite sides often have good relationships.
比如  罗密欧与朱丽叶
You know, Romeo and Juliet...
《西区故事》里的托尼和玛利亚
Tony and Maria from West Side Story,
《阿凡达》里那个谁和那大蓝妞
what's-his-name and the big blue chick in Avatar.
我要去掷球了
I'm gonna bowl now.
人球合一  霍华德
Be the ball, Howard.
别烦我  谢尔顿
Leave me alone, Sheldon.
你没做到人球合一
You weren't the ball.
谢谢
Hey, thanks.
很好玩是吧
This is fun, huh?
对呀
Yeah.
很高兴我们能出来  来点体育锻炼
It's good that we got out and did something physical.
能分散下注意力
Gets us out of our heads.
人一旦纠结什么事
You get in your head,
很容易就会想多  钻牛角尖  心神不宁还烦恼
you start to overthink, overanalyze,obsess, you worry.
但今晚咱不这样
That's not what we're doing tonight.
今晚咱就专心玩保龄球
Tonight we're just throwing a ball at some pins.
对  就是这样
Yeah, that's right.
也许有一天  未来的某一天 你也会爱回我
and someday-- we don't know when-- maybe you'll love me back.
唔  该我了
Ooh, I'm up.
谢尔顿  谢尔顿  谢尔顿  加油
Shel-don! Shel-don! Shel-don! Shel-don!
不好意思
Excuse me.
真不知道你们是在为谁加油  我现在可是球哦
I don't know who you're chanting for as I am currently the ball.
球球  加油
The ball! The ball!
The ball! The ball! The ball! The ball!
感谢上帝
Thank you, Jesus!
我妈肯定会这么说
As my mother would say.
很高兴你跟你男友言归于好了
I'm glad you patched things up with your boyfriend.
是呀  我也是
Oh, yeah, me, too.
在你毫无准备的时候  面对突如其来的示爱
It's always tough when the "L" bomb gets dropped
一向都很难处理的
and you're not ready for it.
说来听听
Tell me about it.
我就跟这么个女孩约会过
I dated this one girl,
我跟她示爱的时候
and I told her that I loved her,
她说她还不确定[自己感情的归属]
and she said she wasn't sure.
然后跟我藕断丝连将近两年时间
And she strung me along for almost two years.
那实在太残忍了
It was brutal.
太遗憾了
Oh, I'm sorry.
谢谢安慰
Thanks.
宁愿她当场就跟我痛快分手
I wish she had just broken up with me right there,
长痛不如短痛
and put me out of my misery.
真的
Really?
对  那样反而好
Yeah, would have been kinder.
威尔  到你了
Wil, you're up.
该我了
Oh, that's me.
你刚让威尔·惠顿给你洗脑了
Did you let Wil Wheaton get in your head?
你在说什么呀
What are you talking about?
他是个魔鬼  最擅长邪恶的心理战
He's evil. He plays evil mind games.
他是不是跟你说他祖母去世了
Did he tell you his grandmother died?
没有
No!
他要是这么说  千万别信
Well, if he does, don't believe it.
他说不定就会骗你他祖母去世博同情
He's not above playing the dead meemaw card.
太棒了
Yes!
好好享受这一时的欢呼吧  威尔·惠顿
Enjoy the accolades now, Wil Wheaton,
但正如你在《星际迷航:下一代》那角色一样命运
but like your time on Star Trek: Next Generation,
你这种自鸣得意  注定只能是一时的
your smug self-satisfaction will be short-lived.
佩妮  该你了
Penny, you're up.
好了  记住  他奶奶还活着
All right, remember, his meemaw's alive
还有  人球合一
and be the ball.
好  明白
Yeah, I got it.
我们必须要打出个全中啊
We really need a strike here.
我知道
I know.
所以慢慢来  集中注意力
So just take your time and concentrate.
莱纳德  别再给我施压了
Leonard, stop pressuring me.
我没在给你施压
I'm not pressuring you.
你就是在  给我让开
Yeah, you are! Just back off!
好吧  抱歉 我这就闭嘴
Okay, I'm sorry. I'll shut up.
我没想让你闭嘴
I didn't mean "shut up."
好  告诉我该怎么说  我照做就是了
Fine. Just tell me what to do, and I'll do it.
不
No...
莱纳德  这对你不公平  我很抱歉
This isn't fair to you, Leonard. I'm sorry.
等等  你这是去哪
Wait! Where are you going?
佩妮  快回来
Penny, come back!
我再给你买冰激凌
I'll get you ice cream!
别  让她走吧
No, let her go.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
她要是走了  就完啦
If she leaves, it's over!
我很确定  我们已经完了[情侣关系]
I'm pretty sure it's already over.
谢尔顿  运气不佳嘛
Tough luck, Sheldon.
是你干的  是不是
You did this, didn't you?
你真以为就为了赢一场保龄球比赛
Do you think I would really break up a couple
我会拆散一对情侣
just to win a bowling match?
不  我想不会吧
No, I suppose not.
很好  你就继续这么想吧
Good. Keep thinking that.
对的  我跟你说
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, yeah, I'm telling you,
Match.com上的妞比eHarmony上的更好泡
the Match.com chicks are much looser than on eHarmony.
好了  我回头再打给你
You know, I-I gotta call you back.
我打赢了个赌  该验收成果了
I won a bet, and it's time to collect.
不知道你们感觉如何  我觉得自己无比强大
I don't know about you, but I feel empowered.